

ABOUT ME

DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Strong ability implement and resolve problems. Interested in website development, web systems, database (relationals and not relations), mobile applications, rest APIs, research new technologies.

Proactive, independent, liable, friendly, reliable. Other talent is giving the best of my daily.

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Discipline
- Management

TECHNICAL SKILLS

NodeJS Rest APIs

.NET (C#, VB.NET)

FLUTTER (Dart)

VueJS

React (Training)

Angular (Training)

JavaScript

TypeScript

Android (native)

jQuery

SQL Server

MySql

MongoDB

FireBase

Luis Angel Castillo Ruelas

5 de Mayo, Culiacán, Sinaloa 80230 MX Phone: 667 2685723

Email: la.castillo09@info.uas.edu.mx

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/luis-angel-castillo-ruelas-52b8a5111/

Experience

Bisoft 2013-2016

- System for pharmacy chains ERP (PharmacySoft).
- System for pharmacy chains from Argentina ERP (UARFA).
- Pawn shop system (PrendaSys) ERP.
- Web system for small pharmacies (PharmacyExpress Web).
- Mobile application to capture sales and orders (Android).
- Web and mobile application for home delivery, price quotation medicine, location from nearest pharmacies (KYKA).
- Electronic bill web system PharmacySoft.

PrimusLabs – Azzule MX 2016 – Present.

 Web system for safety food audits. System that offers certification for crop operations and minimally processed products (Azzule Auditing Software).

Education

- University: Degree Computer Science, Culiacán Sinaloa MX 2009 –
 2013 (Autonomous University of Sinaloa)
- High school: Vladimir Ilich Lenin, Eldorado Sinaloa 2006 -2009 (Autonomous University of Sinaloa).
- Middle school: Telesecundaria Federalizada #176.

English

House of Learning





